hello everybody and I want to talk about
the number one business that I would
start if I was just getting started
let's say that I lost everything in 2024
what's the best use of your time uh this
year so for those of you that haven't
met yet my name is Jeremiah Kowski and I
have built multiple coaching online
course mentoring businesses to over $10
million a year and I help Mentor
beginner coaches on how to do this and
how to get started with that now there's
a number of different business models
that you can start you could do
e-commerce you could do affiliate
marketing you could do Master reseller
rights you could do Drop Shipping um but
what my favorite is is online courses
and a step further from that which is
online mentoring and coaching and here's
why that is number one you don't need to
Source a bunch of products from other
places people things like that that that
are out there what you can do is you can
literally just use a camera like this on
your computer or your cell phone and
create something that you can sell for
$500 to $2,000 that's a value now what
would you say would have that much value
to be able to sell well if you're
solving a problem for somebody a
solution for them that they're looking
for you might be saying well Jeremiah I
don't know if I have anything I could
solve problems with I'm going to show
you by the end of this video that you
actually do have that but why would I
start this right now cuz if you look
around there's a lot of competition you
got YouTube you got AI all of this why
is this the best business to start right
now well here's
why
because all these other businesses that
are out there actually have take way
more effort to reach profitability they
take more staff they're riskier and more
time and I'm going to give you some
examples of this so
e-commerce you could have you have to
ship things out you have to find the
products and and then here's the other
thing because you're not the one making
the product yourself other people can
make it as well or they can find
somebody that has the same product and
then now your competition has basically
eaten your lunch because they have more
money than you and here's the other
thing is that there are billionaires
that are actually buying up companies
called rollup companies that are in the
e-commerce space and it's very very
difficult to make money in that space
maybe you want to do Airbnb or something
like that
well Airbnb is kind of risky because if
you don't have renters you're stuck with
the the
mortgage if you're doing affiliate
marketing you're selling somebody else's
product by taking a portion of it and so
all of these things again it's like well
I don't have to do work the products
already created there it sells itself
that type of a
thing a lot of people think that and I
thought that back in the day you know
when I got started in my own business I
had done a lot of affiliate marketing
back in the day and and I thought that
this was cool because I didn't have to
risk my reputation create content put
myself out there and instead I would
just be promoting somebody else okay
this is the same mindset behind
e-commerce this is the same mindset
behind uh a lot of the different
businesses that are out there other than
coaching and courses and the reason why
a lot of people also don't do coaching
courses they like well it's not a real
business I'll tell you it's more of a
real business than than anything else
that's out there because it's going to
challenge more of what's inside of you
to get things
done network marketing again they can
change the Compensation Plan people are
tired of network marketing opportunities
but the reason why coaches and cour and
courses are so good coaching courses are
so good is because you are actually
solving a problem that somebody has
somebody has an
issue that is not working for them
they're trying to figure something out
there's something that they need help
with and so then what you're able to do
is you're able to package that
information here's the best part about
it is that you can go find that
information bring it together and listen
I'm not encouraging just like reading a
bunch of stuff in a book and then
teaching it in a course if you're going
to be teaching marketing courses if
you're going to be teaching sales have a
track record be an expert there's not a
lot of people that are out there that
can even say that and I'm actually one
of those few people that actually
qualifies in that category because I've
been doing it for so long
successfully but what you can do is you
can take whatever knowledge or skill
that you have experience that you have
and I want you to think about this
there's got to be at least a thousand
people out there and I know thousands a
lot of people like it's not a lot of
people but there's got to be let's say a
hundred people you that they want to
learn how to do the thing that you know
how to do better than anybody else and
you might say well you know there's
people that are better than me we got
to our brain can come up with a thousand
in one reasons why we're not good enough
we're not ready yet and other people are
more skilled and and and and we're going
to
lose and so the first thing you got to
do is train your brain out of that
excuse of holism that addiction to
creating reasons why it's not going to
work for you and I don't mean that it's
not offensive
cuz I was a person that did that for
years I was in this industry for 21
years and made reasons and excuses why I
couldn't create content why I couldn't
go go sell courses why I wasn't willing
to do certain things because I was
worried about how I looked my reputation
what people would think about me if I
looked good sounded good did all the
right things instead of just packaging
something simply selling it putting
myself out there and I could tell you if
I had started doing this this years ago
and I actually knew and learned about
this I don't know where I would be today
but I'll tell you it be it would be
exceptional and I'm in an exceptional
place right now we have a seven figure
business but I'm talking like you know
some of y'all might know my mom's story
she actually has generated over $100
million in the coaching and course space
and she got started doing this in
business over 30 years ago with
e-commerce and then she transitioned
over to network marketing and then she
transitioned over to selling courses and
training and all of this and now she
invests in the stock market and is
semi-retired and so again like that's
where that's where I'm headed right now
in my own trajectory is to be able to do
exactly that because this industry
coaching courses provides you with an
exceptional ability to write your own
paycheck you're not subject to what
everybody else says that you are worth
or should be worth or how much you know
things how much money you can make is
not dictated by a boss it's not dictated
by an affiliate strategy or how much the
market sells stuff for even I want you
to think about that because you can sell
a course for thousands of dollars that
might only take you a few hours to
create okay and so that's why in
2024 this is exactly what I would start
with as far as a course to create I
don't know if I said 2020 earlier but
anyways
2024 living in the past um and so what I
want to encourage you is this is that
it's not rocket science to get started I
meet a lot of people where they are
struggling to decide what idea should I
start with what strategy should I pick
with this and they're overthinking the
whole
process when it comes to the technical
aspects of it you can literally record
your content either on your phone you
can use an app like OBS right here on
your computer very simple and easy to
use to record content right here you can
even use the camera app on your computer
you can use a platform like think if.com
to be able to to sell your course you
can even use a platform like systemi IO
which is free to be able to sell your
courses so there's so many things when
it comes to the technology that's out
there to get started this is one of the
things that I Mentor people on inside of
my coaching program is is what those
steps are to take to be able
to not just build a course but actually
make money with it now here's the skills
that you need to learn
is you got to stop overthinking the
training side of it and the course
creation side of it that's the easiest
part of it because all you got to do is
just press record create some modules
put it together it take it doesn't take
a long time and
then you start marketing you start
selling it you
start finding people that want to buy
that thing that you're creating okay and
so I think that this is one of those one
of those strategies that once you can
learn how to get a product created or
you even can just map it out you can use
AI tools like chat GPT to map out ideas
for what you want your course to look
like you can go in here you know map out
an idea for a course on dog grooming 8
modules and you don't need to create all
eight modules but you could literally
just use the ideas that come from chat
GPT to create a course and then start
recording the lessons that you know you
could do take a look at the ideas that
it gives you and then pick a few of
those ideas and start recording them
then we go out there and we create an
offer and what is an offer an offer is
something that basically takes what our
course is what our idea is and we
package it in a way that's appealing and
attractive to people and that's what I
work with people with inside of my
accelerator program and I'd love to work
with you on is putting their offer
together how do we sell an offer how do
we find the people that are going to buy
our offer so that we can start to move
the needle forward in our business you
know one of the things that I find that
a lot of people do is that they get so
caught up in their head thinking about
well is this the right thing to do am I
going on the right path of this and
we're so worried about what everybody
thinks about us you got to get rid of
two things perfectionism and fear of
other people's approach approval or
disapproval and instead just go out
there do your best have fun with it
really like that's a strategy right
there it's a legitimate strategy to just
have fun with it to go out there to see
what happens to see who engages with you
when you launch a piece of content or a
training or something out there to reach
the kind of people that you're looking
to
reach and then you can sell to those
people and learning the skill of sales
Lear learning how to communicate in a
way that gets people to buy from you it
all comes from your confidence it comes
from how much you believe in the thing
that you've created you know often times
when we're so worried about other
people's approval when we're so worried
about them liking us what they think
about us doing all the right things and
I'm not telling you to do all the wrong
things I'm not telling you to to to to
to do anything that's that's bad or
immoral or
unethical but we're so concerned with oh
I'm going to ask accidentally make a
mistake or I'm going to miss something
and our fear of missing things Keeps Us
locked up in inaction and so when you
can learn to take imperfect action put
something out there experiment adopt
what's called an experimentation mindset
adopt what's called an alpha release
approach where you're willing to release
an idea even if it's not completed 100%
you're willing to put it out there just
to see what happens just to see who
engages with it when you do this you
will be shocked as to what happens and
how many people you attract to you
overall now the nitty-gritty pieces of
this are actually way simpler than a lot
of people make it you record the content
you put it onto a learning platform and
then you create an offer that attracts
those people to you to buy from you and
we can do this either through social
media we can do this through paid
advertising through Facebook
ads and and by the way it's not even
expense if you're using paid advertising
if it's making you way more money than
you're
spending but you have to learn this one
thing and this is the key
communication I'm not saying that you
don't know how to communicate you don't
know how to talk you don't talk
good I'm saying that there's a there's a
Cadence and a methodology of how we
communicate how we verbalize things how
we string sentences together that
creates
engagement it creates buying temperature
which is where somebody feels the desire
to make a purchase and it increases the
level of Desire that people have when
you're creating an offer with a course
what you got to do is you got to take
your course this is the what that you're
selling and then you attach it to the
the deepest desire that somebody has and
then you learn to communicate that
desire in a way that infectiously
inspires them to take action and do
something with it okay and this is a
this is a this is a process that I
Mentor my clients on is how to do this
how do we do this with our marketing how
do we do this with our communication how
do we do this with what we create in our
video content in our advertisements in
our presentations to be able to do
this you know a lot of people have this
idea that if I could just create value
people are going to buy from me that
they're going to become a client because
I made all this valuable information
because it's got so much value they're
going to want to invest into it
unfortunately that's not the way it
works you got to learn how to Market s
and persuade people tap into the
emotional buying drivers in their mind
to get them to take action you want to
attract people to you create an
attraction
methodology that draws people to you
that brings them towards
you not just because of the value but
what they're going to get from them and
the fact that it's the number one thing
that they desire more than anything else
so you figure out what is the desire
that this person has what is the thing
that they want more than anything else
and then you start delivering that to
them in every possible way now I'll tell
you this here's an example as well what
I'm talking about here when it comes to
marketing it's also a strategy for
leadership it's a strategy for how we
interact with our friends and our family
and when you do it from an authentic
place not a manipulative place not a
place I'm doing this to get something
but GA to create the best experience and
environment for those that are around
you you know if I with my wife create an
environment she's pregnant she's about 7
months pregnant and when she wakes up in
the morning the dishes are done and and
the house is cleaned up her stress
levels are lower and now our family is
thriving and we're starting to pay off
our bills faster and we're starting to
to dream for things in the future
because we get out of that figh ORF
flight State and that's one of the
biggest things that when you're
marketing when you're selling you want
to
create a safe atmosphere for the people
that you're selling to that you're
marketing to no matter what that
is it's just like in relationship when
we're in relationship with somebody we
we want to create an environment that is
conducive to that we you know if I just
showed up and I'm like well I'm giving
you the money I'm paying the
bills what more do you want from me to
my wife like that's rude that's abusive
and yet we literally come to the table
like that you know if I went on a date
when I met my wife and I was like all
right you want to marry me like the
first date
like it's not that's not that's not
that's not good and yet that's the
attitude that most people have when
they're marketing when they're
selling and they're desperate they're
looking for people's approval they're
desperate for other people's approval
will you notice me type of
energy so we have to shift out of
desperate energy we have to shift out of
what we call brokem
mindedness you know being broke isn't
something for you to be ashamed of but
it is something for you to choose to
change and it starts with how you
think and how we talk and how we
communicate and the people we hang out
with and the things that we do every
single day that is what changes our life
and when you show up if you're trying to
build a business if you're trying to
create a course or a program and Market
it and you're brokem minded in how
you're communicating it's no wonder that
nobody wants to buy from you as far as
that goes so we have to learn how to be
powerful how to show up with authority
and how to communicate in a way that
people want to be around they want to
learn from they want to spend time with
they want to get to know us and dive
deeper into what is there what can I get
out of this and how amazing is this as
far as that goes and so what happens is
when you do this when you bring all of
these pieces
together it creates a
Synergy that feels
contagious and so when you have
something of value something that solves
a problem for somebody and then you find
the right people that are looking for it
and you use your language you're
messaging you use images we can generate
even some images with AI that tell the
story graphics and photos and you can
start to raise up that buying
temperature and desire inside of your
inside of the person that you're
marketing to the chances of them buying
the thing that you're offering and not
saying no to it are extremely high
because it's exactly what they're
looking for you know if I go to the
store and I see something that just my
mouth starts watering when I see it I'm
going to want to buy that
thing you want in a way your course to
be mouth now it's not like people are
going to eat it but like there's a
version of mouthwatering that happens
mentally and intelligently when people
see something that solves a problem for
them have you ever seen something where
you found a course or a training or a
YouTube video that literally solves
everything that you're looking for and
you're just you get so excited inside
like you're
like whoa this is the best thing I've
ever seen so in you're marketing that's
what you create and you create that
buying
temperature and then it becomes
automatic that people buy from you and
this is exactly what I Mentor people
with inside of our coaching program
inside of my client growth accelerator
program and so listen if you're somebody
that wants to learn how to attract the
right people to you how to build up that
desire that people have to buy that
thing from you to come into your space
and to purchase from you and what are
the strategies to do this how do we do
this with our marketing it goes beyond
just tools and and it goes beyond just
um soft softwares and Facebook ads it's
about learning to communicate in a way
that gets people to take action and gets
people to go from oh I'm just a little
interested in that to whoa I need that
okay and so when it comes to you
creating a course we also put that into
our courses we put that into how we
communicate in our courses we put that
into how we teach how we mentor
to create engaging content that people
they they love and they they're they're
drawn into and they want to listen to
and there's a process and a system and a
framework on how to do that that I
Mentor people with inside of my
accelerator program so if I was starting
a business today in 2024 that's exactly
what I would do is I would I would from
scratch and that's exactly the business
that I help people start and I help them
grow and help them build is creating
courses and then coaching and then
mentoring people learning how to grow in
the confidence and belief that they have
value to offer to
people and then how do we communicate it
in a way to reach people on the internet
that don't know who we are they're
strangers on the internet they have no
idea who we are how do we find those
right people at the right time attract
them into our space with either our
social media content or paid
advertising and then we can present to
them the incredible solution that we
have to offer them so literally what
you're doing is you're finding the right
people at the right time that want the
thing that you offer you don't need to
hard sell them because they already want
it they already desire it all you got to
do is build trust with them that you're
the best one for them to work with you
might say well there's better people
than me that are out there can I tell
you break that thinking where you're
comparing yourself to other people and
you're thinking oh I'm not good enough
I'm not able to show up good enough in
this way and start realizing the
beautiful value and incredible nature of
what's inside of
you and then watch things start to come
together for you in your life and your
business better than you ever imagined
listen I'd love to work with you inside
my accelerator program to do this to put
all these pieces together for you to
work with you to create multiple six
figures of results like we have for our
clients you know I can I can actually
pull up on here on a page we have
different different clients that we've
worked with
that we've created results for like Rick
Peno right here helped him generate over
eight figures in his
business like Joshua Giles right here
seven figures coaching Sandy Kowski nine
figures
generated here's Kim Wright over 20,000
in sales with a real estate offer in a
down Market Ian Carroll helped to make
over $40,000 a month in his business Dr
sha deep over $112,000 in sales
this first campaign running and you can
read these on our site right here Judy
$37,000 in her first month working with
us doing what I say and
teach and we have testimony after
testimony after testimony of people just
like you that have been able to become
successful in their businesses by
learning how to communicate find the
right people and reach those people at
the right time with the right message
all right so listen stay plugged into my
channel here subscribe and make sure to
join us in my accelerator program we'd
love to have you in there as a client
talk soon